我们有182名病人
We have 182 patients.
大多数病人样貌相当的畸形恐怖 这是近亲交配与繁殖必然的结果
Most are horribly deformed, due to inbreeding and birth defects.
C区域 安全指数相当高
Ward "C" is high security.
每一个病人在这里都应该得到我们的尊重 对别人或对自己都是非常危险的
Each patient in here should be considered dangerous or a danger to himself.
没有一个人能通过这道门进出
No one can get in or out without first passing through this door.
如果发生火灾 我们可以打开所有的小房间逃生
We can open all the cells at once in case of fire…
但是每次打开门都要遵守一项协议
but the protocol is one cell open at a time.
谢谢 查理
Thanks, Charlie.
不客气 老板
No problem, boss.
我明白你在想什么 但我们必须检查他们的东西
I know what you're thinking. But we have to do this for their own good.
这里可不是监狱
This is not a prison.
如果有可能的话 我们希望病人可以完全的康复
We hope to rehabilitate the patients if at all possible…
并且希望他们可以重返社会
and have them rejoin the general population.
在所有小房间都打开之前 你必须有一个秩序…
Before any cell is opened, you must have an orderly…
鲍比！鲍比！
Bobby! Bobby!
我们走吧！
Let go!
- 你还好吧？ - 还好
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
这真让我感到惊讶 就这样
That just surprised me. That's all.
你不应该越过黄线到处闲逛
You shouldn't wander past the yellow lines.
他们能够并且会抓住你
They can and will grab you from their cells.
他们是希利克兄弟
These are the Hilliker brothers.
我们称他们“希利克太太”因为当我们找到他们的时候
We call them that because Mrs. Hilliker found them in the woods…
他们正站在尸体的身上在啃食 我们认为那是他们的双亲
standing over the partially eaten remains of what we think were their parents.
非婚生子女非常的漂亮
And the little bastards are smart.
可以相当肯定的说 医院里的大多数病人都相当的危险
Definitely the most dangerous patients in the hospital.
你们都只是孩子 大多数的危险？
They're just kids. And the most dangerous?
是的 请相信我
Yes. Trust me.
其中最年轻的一个 用牙齿把自己的手指一点点的啃掉了
The youngest one, the one sucking on the stump of his hand?
- 不是吧？ - 他已经啃掉另外的两个手指了
- Yeah? - He chewed off his other two fingers.
我们从来没有找他们 我们觉得他会把他们都吃了
We never found them. We think he ate them.
中间的那个孩子 他拿叉子把自己的棕色的眼睛捅下来了
The middle child. He poked out his own eye with a fork.
并且 在护士的面前吃掉它
Ate it right in front of a nurse.
那个带着面具的那个大男孩呢？
And the large boy with the mask?
他有一排异常巨大的牙齿 他在墙上把自己的牙齿磨的非常尖利
He has abnormally large teeth, which he was sharpening on the stone walls.
我们在他又咬了几个看护者之后 我们给他戴上了面具
We put the mask on him after he bit several orderlies.
磨尖牙齿？他怎么能忍受这样的疼痛？
Sharpening? How can he tolerate the pain?
这些孩子们最入迷的就是这些事情 他们不会感觉到疼痛
That's the fascinating thing about these children. They can't feel pain.
他们有先天性痛觉丧失的记录
They have an advanced form of congenital analgesia.
- 极端罕见 - 是的
- That's extremely rare. - Yes.
但在同质社会这样的情形更普遍
But it's more prevalent in homogeneous societies.
- 类似于西佛尼吉亚州近亲繁殖群落 - 正解
- Like the inbred communities of West Virginia. - Exactly.
他们可以聊天吗？
Can they talk?
他们只能咕噜咕噜的说话 用手势表达 那是他们的语言
Just grunts and gestures. It's their own language.
一旦进入他们的房间 你就绝对无法出来
Never turn your back on them or their cell.
恕我冒犯 医生 但这些都超出你的治疗方法之外 音乐舞台剧还是其他别的
No offense, Doctor. But these are beyond your kind of therapy. Musical or otherwise.
我不喜欢和他们一起工作 赖安医生
I'd like to work with them, Dr. Ryan.
也许等一会可以吧
Maybe after a while.
为什么我们不安全的玩呢？
Why don't we play it safe for now?
来吧 我要让你在医院里休息下
Come on. I'll show you the rest of the hospital.
当然
Sure.
嘿 让我离开这里！
Hey, get me out of here!
出去
Gone.
来这里 过来 给我出去
Come here. Get in here. Get me out.
嘿 让我出去！
Hey! Let me out!
嘿 护卫！
Hey, guard!
不！不！
No! No!
不！哦 不！
No! Oh, no!
不！
No!
如果你让我走的话 我可以帮你
I can help you if you just let me go.
我可以帮你
I can help you.
不！
No!
哦 我的天 哦 上帝
Oh, my God. Oh, God.
不！
No!
哦 拜托 别这样对我
Oh, please. Don't do this to me.
男孩们 你不需要这样对我
Boys, you don't need to do this to me.
求求你！天啊 不！
Please! God, no!
哦！哦！
Ohh! Ohh!
《致命弯道4：血腥起源》
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
- 哦 我的天！ - 你喜欢那样？
- Oh, my God! - You like that?
- 是的 - 是的？
- Yeah. - Yeah?
来吧
Come on.
你们这些野生荡妇
You guys are a bunch of slut monkeys.
我可没听见敲门？
Heard of knocking?
波特都走了 凯尔和克莱尔大概在山上等着我们
Porter has already left. Kyle and Claire are probably waiting for us on the mountain.
我的车在五分钟内会离开 不管你们这些家伙在还是不在
My car leaves in five minutes whether you guys wanna be in it or not.
为什么不来放松一会呢？
Why don't you just relax and jump underneath the covers for a bit?
我不觉得布丽姬特会非常的赏识
I don't think Bridget would appreciate that very much.
我不会介意的
I don't really mind.
- 我也不会介意 - 嘿！
- I don't mind either. - Hey!
- 开个玩笑 - 五分钟 小兔子们
- Just kidding. - Five minutes, you rabbits.
为什么今年我们不去埃斯佩？波特的小木屋有够烂的
Why aren't we going to Aspen this year? Porter's cabin sucks.
因为我的爸爸失去了他退休的机会 所以不得不卖掉他的房子
Because my dad lost his retirement and had to sell the house.
- 真的？ - 是啊 当他被找到的时候 你应该已经看见他了
- Really? - Yeah, you should have seen him when he found out.
我觉得他想从桥上跳下去 嘿！
I thought he was gonna jump off a bridge. Hey.
- 嘿！ - 嘿！
- Hey! - Hey!
- Hey. - Hey.
波特在哪里？
Where's Porter?
- 他直接回小木屋 让身体发汗去了 - 哦
- He went on ahead to get the cabin warmed up. - Oh.
他肯定是病了或者怎么样了 因为波特经常随身带一个热水袋
He must be sick or something 'cause usually Porter's a douche bag.
- 只是对你 - 我知道 那跟什么有关？
- Only to you. - I know. What's that all about?
嗯 我不知道 也许这就是你让我过来的原因？
Um, I don't know. Maybe it's because you keep making passes at me?
他真的不可靠？
He's that insecure?
你是不是有什么事想告诉我？肯尼娅？我在这里是因为我的妹妹
Is there something you want to tell me, Kenia? I'm here for a sister.
啊 滚开 滚开
Uh, fuck off. Fuck off.
- 嘿 你好么？ - 嘿 兄弟
- Hey. How you doing? - Hey, man.
- 这是我的交通工具 - 嗨
- This is my ride. - Hi.
嘿！
Hey!
- 我太兴奋了 不是么？ - 我是如此的兴奋
- I am so excited. Aren't you? - I'm so excited.
- 嘿 兄弟 抱歉来晚了 - 嘿
- Hey, guys. Sorry we're late. - Hey.
- 都是丹尼尔的错 - 这条路可真糟
- Daniel's fault. - The roads were bad.
那是谁开的车？
So who's driving?
我开的
I'm driving.
你开车就像个小女孩 我想开快车
You drive like a girl. I want to go fast.
谢谢 真的不错
Thanks. Real nice.
那、你想搭着我去
Then you're gonna wanna ride with me.
- 好的 - 你们来了
- Okay. - There you go.
嘿 凯尔？我刚听到电台新闻报告 会有一个巨大的风暴经过这里
Hey, Kyle? I heard on the radio there's a huge storm blowing in.
你觉得呢 也许我们该等等再走？还是等明天再说？
You think maybe we wait? Do this tomorrow?
会没事的 公主 一小时内我们会一直待在小木屋里
It'll be okay, princess. We'll be at the cabin in an hour.
好的 开始打吧！
All right. Let's hit it!
- 好极了！ - 是的
- All right! - Yeah.
- 那些车怎么样？开到公园应该没事吧？ - 哦 我的天啊！
- What about the cars? Are we okay to park here? - Oh, my gosh.
杰西 丹尼尔 你还担心一切吗？他们都会没事的
Jesus, Daniel. You got to worry about everything? They'll be fine.
我们要走了
Let's go already.
好的 不好意思
All right. Excuse me.
你是说真的？丹尼尔？
Seriously, Daniel?
- 干嘛？ - 看看丹尼尔
- What? - Check out Daniel.
不是么？安全第一！
What? Safety first!
我很乐意看到你在雪地车上掉下来的样子
I'd like to see you laughing when you fall off your snowmobile.
- 啊…哦！ - 好的 出发吧！
- Uh-huh. - All right. Let's go!
- 出发！ - 快出发吧！
- Let's go! - Let's do it!
来吧 我们已经准备好了
Come on. Let's go already.
好的 我们走！
All right. Let's go!
过来了！
Up close!
来吧 我们走！
Come on. Let's go!
嘿 女士们！
Hey, ladies!
前进！
gotta go!
- 你迷路了 - 不 我没有
- You're lost. - No, I'm not.
就承认了吧
Just admit it.
白痴 该死的 这里被冻住了
Idiot. It's frickin' freezing out here.
过了一个半小时 肯定又降了20度
It must have dropped 20 degrees in the last half an hour.
离黎明还有一个小时
We've got an hour of daylight left.
这里的风暴随时会刮过来
There's a huge storm blowing in any minute now.
保持点风度 好吗？
Just give me a minute to get my bearings, all right?
- 嘿？嘿！ - 什么？
- Hey? Hey! - What?
我们应该开到左边那个斜坡
We should be going left up there over that hill.
不 我曾和波特去那个小木屋一百次 是在右边 我很肯定
No, I've been to the cabin a hundred times with Porter. It's right. I'm sure of it.
我们应该开到不远处的半山腰那里
We need to get over that far ridge over there.
好吧 我们就去那里 我也快冻死了
Fine. Then let's go. I'm freezing too.
- 好的 来吧 - 来吧 兄弟们
- Yeah. Come on! - Come on, guys.
是的
Yeah.
他开错了方向 我知道的
He's making a wrong turn. I know it.
抱歉 兄弟们！我觉得我开反了方向！
Sorry, guys! I guess I got turned around!
如果我们不能很快找到避难所 我们都会冻死的！
If we don't find some shelter soon, we're gonna freeze to death!
我说过我们要准确的原路开回去！
I say we go back the exact same way we came!
是的 那倒不算是一个糟糕的主意 我们开回去
Yeah, that's not a bad idea. Let's turn around…
掉头下山 沿着你在雪中来时的车的轨迹开回去
head back down the mountain, and follow your tracks in the snow.
什么轨迹？雪中的车的轨迹都被刮走了
What tracks? They've been blown away.
- 那是什么？ - 那是什么？
- What's that? - What's what?
那个巨大的、黑色的风暴沿着山腰刮过来了
That huge, dark shape along the side of the ridge.
我认为那是个建筑物！
I think it's a building!
该死的…啊！我们得救了！
Frickin'-A! We're saved.
- 来吧！ 快来！ - 好的
- Come on! Let's go! - Okay.
快冻死了！
I'm freezing!
快点 快点
Come on. Come on.
别滑到了！
Don't slip!
- 谢天谢地 - 布丽姬特 我可以吻你了
- Thank God. - Bridget, I could kiss you.
- 哦 - 门是打开的 进来
- Ohh. - It's open. Come on.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
亲爱的 你想要你的滑雪板装备吗？
Honey, you want your ski gear?
离它远点 我会拿回我的背包 它也被冻住了！
Leave it. I've got my bag, and it's freezing!
- 哦！ - 我快冻死了
- Ohh! - I'm freezing.
- 这到底是什么地方？ - 或许是一间旧医院？
- What is this place? - An old hospital maybe?
- 哦 看起来就像是在晚上参观一样 - 棒极了
- Well, it looks like we're visiting for the night. - Great.
可以进去吗？
Shall we?
这到底是什么地方？
What is this place?
- 该死的 - 为什么这里如此温暖？
- Holy crap. - Why is it so warm in here?
或许这里有管理员或者门警什么的吧
Maybe there's a janitor here or something.
他们大概在烧锅炉所以管道才不会结冰的吧
They probably keep the boiler going so the pipes won't freeze.
竟然能找到这个地方来 你可真是走运啊！
You're really lucky this place was here, man.
- 真让人毛骨悚然 - 哦 这里落满了灰尘
- Creepy. - Oh, it's dusty.
- 到处都是灰 - 好恶心！
- Gross. - It's disgusting!
- 我高兴的只是我们进来了 - 那你找到了么？
- I'm just glad we're inside. - Ew! Did you find that in here?
- 找到了 - 别碰它
- Yeah. - Don't touch it.
真吓人！
That's so creepy!
你们找到电灯开关了没？
Can you guys find something to burn?
一些木制品 或是家具什么的？
Scrap wood or furniture? Something.
- 是啊 我们看见了 - 是的
- Yeah. We're on it. - Yeah.
- 波特呢？ - 他就像我们期待的那样
- What about Porter? - He's going to be expecting us.
你觉不觉得 他在这个温度下会出去的 不是么？
You don't think he'd go out in this weather, do you?
当然不 波特太聪明了才不会那样做呢
No. Porter's way too smart for that.
你或许应该给他打个电话 让他知道我们很安全
Maybe you should give him a call. Let him know we're safe.
好主意
Good idea.
我手机服务中断了 真是奇怪 你们的手机有信号吗？
My freaking cell service sucks. Does anyone have a signal?
我看看 没信号
I'll check. No.
- 什么都没有 - 该死
- Nothing. - Shit.
肯尼娅 波特是个聪明的家伙
Kenia, Porter's a really smart guy.
他应该知道这种天气我们不会外出
He's gonna know we wouldn't go out in this weather.
你是说波特变聪明了？
You're talking about Porter being smart?
你在说哪个波特？
Which Porter is that?
恩 他是那群混蛋中比凯尔更聪明一点的家伙 谁让我们迷路了 记得吗？
Well, he's a hell of a lot smarter than Kyle, who got us lost. Remember?
我可没说凯尔也聪明
I didn't say Kyle was smart either.
波特现在或许在温暖舒适的房间正快活吧
Porter's probably nice and toasty right now.
是的 我希望如此
Yeah. I hope so.
好的 谁准备了小型烧烤？是你吗？
Okay. Who's up for a weenie roast? You?
你？还是你？
You? You?
我知道是你
I know you are.
好吧
All right.
拿了没？
Got it?
嘿
Hey.
过来 过来 过来
Scooch, scooch, scooch.
好吧 各位 我只是想对各位说声抱歉 我犯了个错误 不该去那边
All right, guys. I just want to say sorry for the mix-up out there.
我知道事情也许变得很糟
I know things could have turned out really bad…
但是我高兴的是我们都还好
but I'm glad we're all okay.
别担心了 兄弟 每个人都可能会发生这种事情的
Don't worry about it, dude. It could have happened to anyone.
还不错 我们都很好 早上我们就回到小木屋里
It's fine. We're all fine. We'll go to the cabin in the morning.
我想 到那个时候天气就会变晴朗的
I think the weather should be clear by then.
我们先找些休息的地方吧
Let's just try to get some rest.
没门！你难道看不见这个地方吗？真是令人难以置信！
No way! Have you seen this place? It's fucking fantastic.
让我们检查下 做一次小小的探险
Let's check it out. Do a little exploring.
非法入侵？
Trespassing?
天 丹尼尔
God, Daniel.
- 好啦 好啦 我和你一起去 - 耶 我也去
- All right. All right. I'll go with you. - Yeah, me too.
你们女孩子呆在一起可以吗？
You girls gonna be okay alone?
- 别再走丢了 - 谢了
- Don't get lost again. - Thanks.
等等 你期望她们会为我们做一顿晚餐吗？
Wait. You expect us girls to cook dinner?
热狗啦！
It's hot dogs.
我认为你们这些女孩可以做得到
I think you ladies can handle that.
恩 也许我不想做
Well, maybe I don't want to.
那好吧 布丽姬特 你不做热狗是吧？
That's right, Bridget. You don't do hot dogs, do ya?
去你的 文森特
Fuck you, Vincent.
我们走
Let's go.
- 等等 我和你一起去 - 那 我也去
- Wait. I'll go with you. - Yeah, me too.
嘿 等等 我也要去
Hey, wait up. I'm coming too.
看看那
check up.
嘿 看看这个
Hey, check this out.
这表示某人最近来过这里
It looks like somebody's been here recently.
猎人可能在春季径流期间用这个来抢劫
Hunters probably use this to hold up in during the spring runoff.
你们是不是觉得这里竟然一个人都没有很奇怪？
Do you guys think anyone would actually be here right now?
我是说 这里可真吓人
I mean, that would be really creepy.
不 没有一个猎人会在这个季节捕猎
No. No one's hunting in this weather.
电锯杀人狂会这么做
Ax murderers do.
只是说说而已
Just saying.
嘿 这个一定就是老板的办公室了
Hey, this must be the head honcho's office.
“布伦丹·赖安医生 参谋长”
"Dr. Brendan Ryan, Chief of Staff."
哦 看看长官有没有什么好东西
Well, let's see if the chief had any good stuff.
哦 这里发生了什么事？
Oh. What the hell happened in here?
嘿 看看外套还有听诊器
Hey, check out this coat and stethoscope.
嘿 詹娜 坐上我的桌子 我们拍一段色情影片
Hey, Jenna, hop on my desk. We're gonna do a porn scene.
- 哦 天 - 我是医生 你是护士
- Oh, God. - Me doctor, you nurse.
- 文森特 你不介意吗？ - 上她吧
- Vince, you mind? - Do her.
我在忙着治疗我的病人
I'm busy with my patients.
嘿！嘿！离我远点！
Hey! Hey! Get away from me!
那么 佩兰小姐
So, Miss Perrin.
这些可怕的噩梦 多久会出现一次？
How long have you been having these reoccurring nightmares?
恩 在我十二岁的时候就开始了
Well, it all started when I was 12.
我、我感觉这个出现在我的房间上
I-I felt this presence in my room at night.
这次是你的第一次吗？
Was this about the time of your first period?
你这个该死的变态 你知道吗？
You're a fucking pervert. You know that?
极端的梦境是年轻女子月经期间最直接的结果
Violent dreams are a direct result of menstruation in young women.
- 你自慰过么？ - 噢
- Had you masturbated yet? - Ew!
你真让人作呕
You're fucking disgusting.
哦 又“中奖”了！
Oh! Jackpot.
看起来这位好好医生是一个酒鬼 有人一口闷的吗？
Looks like the good doctor was a boozer. Anyone for a snort?
请告诉我你不想喝
Please tell me you're not gonna drink that.
珍藏的30年的瓶装苏格兰酒
It's a 30-year-old bottle of scotch.
30年前的了 詹娜 还未启封
Thirty years ago, Jenna. Unopened.
入口很清爽、顺滑
Mmm. That is smooth.
小姑娘
To pussy.
哦！
Ooh!
- 真该死 - 什么？
- Holy shit. - What?
真是一团糟
That's some fucked-up shit.
那到底是什么？
What the fuck is that?
一个人
A person.
那个人怎么了？
What the hell happened to him?
- 在那里出生 - 穷婊子
- Born that way. - Poor son of a bitch.
哦 那太邪恶了
Oh! That is so wrong.
- 天啊！ - 这里到底是什么地方？
- Jesus! - What was this place?
根据历史记录 这里是格伦威尔疗养院
According to the records, it was the Glenville Sanatorium.
- 所有的疯子都被关起来了？ - 当然不是 这里是疗养院
- Isn't that where crazy people are locked up? - No, that's a sanitarium.
疗养院是从医院其他的隔离病人中选出来的
A sanatorium is a hospital that isolates sick people from the rest of the population.
这些人到底发生了什么事情？
What was wrong with these people?
我不知道
I don't know.
我能告诉你的就只是他们是畸形人
They're all deformed from what I can tell.
我想带些东西看看
I'm gonna take some of these and read them.
我只是希望没有传染性
I just hope it wasn't contagious.
- 好吧 - 来了 我们应该回去和其他人会合啦
- All right. - Come on. We should get back to the others.
好吧
Yeah.
好主意
That's a great idea.
当你喝醉了再看他 他会变得很可爱的
He's kind of cute when you're stoned.
你知道 就像E.T外星人那一类
You know, in like an E. T. kind of way.
喔 宝贝
Wow, babe.
你知道 你的思绪比我想象的更加的混乱
You know, you're a lot more fucked up than I thought you were.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 我找到一间病房 里面有病床和便便
Hey, I found a patient ward that's got beds and shit.
哦 真讨厌 我可不想在那么脏的床垫上睡觉
Oh, gross. I don't want to sleep on a filthy mattress.
我们会躺在睡眠袋里睡觉
We'll lay our sleeping bags over the top.
总比睡在坚硬的地板上要好 并且 我们找到了一点内部资料
It's better than sleeping on the hard floor. Plus, we get a little privacy.
好的
Okay.
我们会回来的 各位
We'll be back, guys.
- 好的 - 晚安 - 再见
- All right. - Night. - So long.
嘿
Hey.
- 你要出去看看吗？ - 当然
- You wanna come check it out? - Sure.
我还不够吗？
I'm not enough?
啊 你是我的
Ah, you are mine.
看见了吗？不算太糟
See? It's not so bad.
好的
Okay.
好的 我想我们都应该选择一个房间
Okay, I say we all pick a room.
然后 每一位都把他们的钥匙放在大酒杯里
And then everyone puts their keys in a bowl…
然后我们每个人选一把钥匙 看看谁睡在谁的房间里
and we pick to see who sleeps with who.
- 别停下 好吗？ - 我也这样想
- You just don't stop, do you? - It's what I do best.
你知道最好
You got that right.
嘿！我想我看见了个人影
Hey! I think I just saw somebody.
鬼魂 真可怕
Ghosts. Awesome.
不 那不是鬼魂 我觉得是一个人
No, it wasn't a ghost. I think it was a person.
喂 这里已经没有人了
Well, there's nobody there now.
如果你想让我带你去看的话 我会的
If you want me to take a look, I will.
不 没有人在这里
No. Nobody here.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
文森特？
Vincent?
这一点都不好笑 文森特！
This isn't funny, Vincent!
文森特 回答我！
Vincent, answer me!
- 我要走了 这一点都不酷 不 - 不 不 不！
- I'm going. This isn't cool. No. - No, no, no!
- 不！ - 别离开我 来
- No! - Don't leave me alone. Come.
文森特
Vincent.
文森特？
Vincent?
你这个混蛋！
You fucking asshole!
冷静点 找点乐趣嘛
Calm down. Trying to have some fun.
哦 我无法相信你！
Oh, I can't believe you!
天啊！他就是一个笨蛋
God! He's such a jerk.
肯尼娅？
Kenia?
- 让开！ - 嘿 怎么了？
- Move! - Hey, what's up?
他就是个混蛋
He's a fucking jerk.
我害怕他们小便 你应该看过
I scared the piss out of them. You should have seen it.
你的智力就像一个10岁的小孩子 你知道 是吧？
You have the mentality of a 10-year-old. You know that, right?
- 好吧 - 我可以进入黑暗的地方
- Okay. - I could have fallen in the dark.
你不知道这个一直恶作剧的
You have no idea of the consequences…
方式很愚蠢吗？
of your stupid, incessant pranks.
我刚才看见一个大型发电机
Well, a place this big has gotta have its own generator.
就是你俩刚才怕黑没进去的地方
And since you two are afraid of the dark…
不过我看见了 我可以去把电发起来 让房间明亮起来
I'll see if I can find it and get some heat and lights started.
没想到 你还挺能干的
Finally, you're doing something useful.
嘿 文森特在很多方面都很能干 不是么 宝贝？
Hey, Vincent can be useful in many ways, can't you, baby?
别吹牛了 宝贝 再见 小家伙
Don't go bragging now, babe. Ciao, kiddies.
你做好了吗？
You doing okay?
好了 那很好 哈？
Okay. That good, huh?
我找到瓦斯了
We got gas.
要是可以启动的话 就让我看看
Let's see if you'll run.
嘿 嘿 嘿！
Hey. Hey, hey!
看到了？我告诉过你他很能干的
See? I told you he was useful.
有时而已
Sometimes.
现在开心吗？
Happy now?
是啊 太谢谢你了
Yes. Thank you so much.
好吧 我们刚才找到了真正酷的东西 过来一起玩吧
All right. Well, let's go have some fun 'cause I found some really cool shit.
好的！
Yeah!
- 好吧 - 来
- All right. - Come.
走 走！我们走吧！
Go, go! Let's go!
获胜者！
The winner!
? And here he comes again?
哦 走 走 走！
Oh, go, go, go!
? Ohh, ohh, ohh?
向右转！ 向右转！
Turn right! Turn right!
? He never had no mercy for me??
出发！
Go!
我做到了 我做到了
I got it. I got it.
这个地方太令人惊讶了 这些怪胎竟然还有观众席
This place is amazing. The freaks had their own auditorium.
你能想象这些家伙在台上表演吗？
Can you imagine those guys up there putting on their own play?
我们把这称为“怪胎秀”
It gives a whole new meaning to the term freak show.
是的 我敢打赌每个人都是大象人的变种
Yeah, I bet everyone was a variation of the Elephant Man.
嘿 他们观看的影片
Hey, they watched movies here.
- 嘿 让我看看那个 - 好的 观影时间
- Hey, let me see that. - Okay, movie time.
- 各位开始兴奋了吗？ - 当然！
- Shall I fire it up? - Yeah!
谁想要爆米花？
Who's up for popcorn?
- 好的 - 是的
- Fine. - Yeah.
他们只是很可怕而已
They're just creepy.
我觉得太糟了
I think it's kind of sad.
我想知道他们发生了什么事
I wonder what happened to them.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道？
You know?
我记得现在这个地方
I remember this place now.
当我还是一个小女孩的时候 我弟弟经常在这里给我讲
My brother used to scare the shit out of me when I was a little girl…
那些用来吓我的乡巴佬的故事
with stories about the hillbillies.
是什么故事？
What stories?
他说这里曾经有一群西佛尼吉亚州的乡巴佬
He said there was a bunch of inbred West Virginia hillbillies…
一直居住在这里 当有人被围困返回的时候
that got rounded up way back when…
他们会回来 把他们都锁在这个医院里
and locked up in this old hospital.
- 哦 我的天 - 他们畸形并不是因为其他的原因所导致的
- Oh, my God. - They're deformed 'cause they kept on screwing each other.
他说 他们并不是一起生活的
He said that's not all they did to each other.
那是什么原因？
What else?
他说 他们互相啃食彼此 食人者
He said they ate each other. Cannibals.
- 你是说真的？ - 这真是一派胡言
- Are you serious? - That's bullshit.
- 就是 就是 - 那只是都市传说
- Yeah, right. - That's an urban legend.
他每次开车穿越“绿蔷薇州”的时候 都会告诉我这个故事
He'd tell me the stories every time we drove through Greenbrier County.
演出结束 各位
Show's over, folks.
- 是的 - 我不想知道你们想干嘛 但是我想睡觉了
- Yeah. - I don't know about you guys, but I am going to bed.
劳伦？
Lauren?
- 嘿 詹娜？一起走吗？ - 好主意
- Hey, Jenna? Wanna go? - That's a good idea.
是啊 做些噩梦
Yeah, for some nightmares.
我们走吧 宝贝 就寝时间
Let's go, baby. Bedtime.
嘿 谁想在早上和我一起跑楼梯 有人一起吗？
Hey, who wants to run the stairs with me in the morning? Anyone?
早起锻炼身体？我想我们要睡了
Wake and exercise? I think I'll sleep in.
我们也一样
Us too.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
我睡不着 我去探险
I can't sleep. I'm gonna go explore.
好的 别和别人一起去
Okay. Don't go fucking with anybody.
他们睡熟了 这也不太酷
They're asleep and it's so not cool.
我知道了 我不会的
I get it. I won't.
我保证
I promise.
嘿 你！谁在哪？
Hey, you! Who's there?
你最好别想玩我 兄弟！
You better not be playing with me, dude!
我要揍了你！
I'll beat the shit out of you!
波特 是你吗？
Porter, is that you?
波特 你什么时候到的？
Porter, when did you get here?
去你的 你想吓我是吧
Holy shit. You scared the hell out of me, man.
这里很不错 不是么？
This place is great, isn't it?
兄弟 你在干嘛？我们回去吧
Dude, what are you doing? Let's go.
兄弟 你睡着了吗？
Dude, are you asleep?
真他妈的该死！
Holy fuck!
文森特？
Vincent?
好极了 我们差不多走出杂草堆了
Great. We're almost out of weed.
恩 是你昨晚在这里抽烟吧
Well, that's 'cause you smoked it all last night.
- 我的衬衣呢？ - 不知道
- Where's my shirt? - I don't know.
- 在这里 - 谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
不用谢
You're welcome.
嘿 你看到文森特了吗？
Hey, have you seen Vincent?
- 没看见 - 没看见？
- No. - No?
他昨晚探险去了 我也找不到他
He went exploring last night, and I can't find him.
你从昨晚起就还没看见他吗？
You haven't seen him since last night?
- 没 - 哦
- No. - Oh.
- 恩 他应该去别的地方了吧 - 我知道
- Well, he's got to be around here somewhere. - I know.
- 我会帮你看看的 - 谢谢
- I'll help you look. - Thanks.
这个地方太大了 他可以在任何地方
This place is so huge. He could be anywhere.
对
Yeah.
嘿 几位 你们看到文森特了吗？
Hey, guys, have you seen Vincent?
- 昨晚就没看到了 没看到 - 没有
- Not since last night, no. - No.
没有？哦
No? Ohh.
我们 额…我们找找文森特吧
We're, uh… We're looking for Vincent.
还没看到他
Haven't seen him.
我倒是不担心 各位 我们又没走完所有的地方
I wouldn't worry about it, guys. We're not going anywhere.
你看过那边了吗？那里可是在下大雪
Have you seen it out there? It's snowing like crazy.
- 嘿 莎拉 你看见文森特了吗？ - 看见了
- Hey, Sara, have you seen Vincent? - Yes.
- 真的么？他在哪儿？ - 我昨晚看见他在偷窥我
- Really? Where is he? - I saw him last night doing his peeping tom bit.
他在看我和布丽姬特
He was watching me and Bridget.
- 那今天早上呢？ - 不 我还没看见他 我一小时前在运动
- What about this morning? - No, I haven't seen him. I've been running for the last hour.
我们开动了 每个人都有早餐吧？
Let's eat. Breakfast anyone?
我们都吃饱了
We'll grab our stuff.
- 文森特怎么了？ - 他要出现了
- What about Vincent? - He'll show up.
我看到你们都下来了
I'll meet you guys down there.
说真的 见鬼去吧！
Seriously. Go to hell.
嘿 你他妈的要去哪里？
Hey, where did all our shit go?
文森特或许我们去食堂用餐就会见到了 兄弟
Vincent's probably trying to mess with us, bro.
别担心 丢些木头在火上
Don't worry about it. Just throw some wood on the fire.
天啊 外边很糟糕
Jesus. It's bad out there.
伙计 你觉得我们应该等风暴过后再走么？
Guys, do you think we should wait for the storm to blow over?
不 你看 我说我们应该打包收拾好 找到文森特 然后离开
No. Look, I say we pack up, we find Vincent, and we get going.
是啊 我们分两组进行
Yeah. Let's split up into two groups though.
丹尼尔 你带着布丽姬特 莎拉 还有劳伦 去看看上面的楼层
Daniel, you take Bridget, Sara and Lauren and check the upper floors.
其他人和我走 我们去看看一楼和地下室
Everyone else come with me. We'll check the first floor and the basement.
我们一个半小时后在观众席见
We'll meet up in the auditorium in half an hour.
我…我还没有吃完
I'm… I'm not done eating.
凯尔 快点 哎呀！
Kyle, come on. Geez.
有没有人觉得我们的东西消失的很奇怪？
Does anyone not think it's weird our stuff is gone?
几位 我们会比预期更早的发现他 然后尽快离开
You guys, the sooner we find him, the quicker we can leave.
走吧
Let's go.
开始吧 公主
Here you go, princess.
我是公主 谢谢
I'm a princess. Thanks.
你觉得很好笑吗？
You think it's funny?
哦 等等！是的
Oh, wait! Yes.
继续走吧
Let's move it.
是啊 很肯定他已经死了
Yeah. He's dead for sure.
闭嘴 凯尔
Shut up, Kyle.
喂 文森特！
Come on, Vincent!
文森特 我们找到食物啦！
Vincent, we've got food!
- 文森特！ - 我再也不喜欢这个了
- Vince! - I really don't like this anymore.
那是什么？
What is that?
哦 那些是什么？
Oh, what is all this?
喂 我们一定要查查看
Well, we're definitely checking this out.
我猜你不用按照顺序…
So, I guess if you didn't follow the program…
- 他们就会把你这些切成薄片 切成一小块一小块的… - 离开这里！
- they had some serious slice and dice… - Get out of here!
我们在找文森特 记得吗？
We're looking for Vincent, remember?
- 记得 - 是的 我们走吧 快点 快点
- Yes. - Yeah. Let's go. Come on. Come on.
- 别做傻事 - 我们离开这吧
- Quit goofing around. - Let's get out of here.
C区域 打开门 我们检查下
Ward "C." Open the door. Let's check this out.
他们像是关动物一样关着他们
They locked them up like animals.
他们看起来像是动物
They look like animals.
来吧 我们过来看看
Come on. Let's keep moving.
那是什么？
What's that?
看起来像是护士站
It looks like a nurse's station.
要是这里遗留了药品的话 文森特肯定会查看的
Vincent definitely would have checked to see if there were any drugs left behind.
是啊 有可能
Yeah, probably.
是血
It's blood.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
好吧 呆在这里 好吗？我去看看后就回来
All right, stay here, okay? I'm gonna check it out.
你觉得是文森特的血吗？
Do you think it's Vincent's?
啊 我是说 他…他…砍伤了什么东西
Uh, I mean, he-he… he could have cut himself on something.
文斯？
Vince?
我是说我们每次经过走廊 我们会看到更多的血迹
Well, I say we each take a hallway. We can cover more ground that way.
对我来说 听起来不错
Sounds good to me.
这条路？
This way?
- 我猜我们走这边 - 我猜的
- I guess we're going this way. - I guess so.
文森特？
Vincent?
我真的开始担心了
I'm really starting to get worried.
- 他会出现的 - 我确信他只是在哪里睡着了
- He'll show up. - I'm sure he just fell asleep somewhere.
他昨晚抽了很多烟
He smoked pretty heavy last night.
他大概喝醉了酒 在迷迷糊糊中不知道走到哪里去了
He's probably stoned right now, in a corner having a bad trip somewhere.
是啊 嘿
Yeah. Hey.
- 找到什么了吗？ - 是的
- Did you guys find anything? - Yeah.
- 什么？- 一小滩血
- What? - A small amount of blood.
- 我们不能独自一人呆在这里 - 你那么说是什么意思？
- We are not alone here. - What do you mean?
有人想要干掉我们
Somebody is fucking with us.
- 什么？ - 我想尽快的出去
- What? - I wanna get the hell outta here now.
他们想把我们都杀死！
They're gonna kill us all!
那个看起来想是波特的夹克
That looks like Porter's jacket.
那是波特的夹克
That is Porter's jacket.
坚持住！
Hang on!
克莱尔！
Claire!
克莱尔！克莱尔！
Claire! Claire!
救救我！克莱尔！
Help! Claire!
别看了！坚持住！
Don't look up! Hold on!
克莱尔！
Claire!
克莱尔 坚持住！
Claire, hold on!
哦 天啊！克莱尔！
Oh, God! Claire!
快点！快点！
Come on! Come on!
该死的门被锁住了！锁起来了！
The fucking door's locked! It's locked!
你们 快过来！
Girls, come on!
快点！
Hurry!
哦 我的上帝！该死！
Oh, my God! Shit!
- 启动不了了！ - 我也是！
- It won't start! - Neither will mine!
该死！
Shit.
他们弄坏了电源线
They've stripped the spark plug wires.
- 我的也是 - 他们弄坏了雪上摩托！
- Mine too. - They sabotaged the fucking snowmobiles!
我们现在该怎么办？
What are we gonna do now?
我们不可能在这场风暴中漫步的
We won't last on foot in this storm.
我们甚至没穿那该死的夹克
We don't even have fucking jackets.
按我说 我们应该回去想出保护我们自己的方法
I say we go back inside and figure out a way to defend ourselves.
- 谁去与那些畸形人在一起？ - 我弟弟告诉我 他们是食人者乡巴佬
- Who the fuck are they? - The cannibal hillbillies my brother told me about.
还有谁要回去？
Who else could it be?
- 你在干嘛？ - 我去找救兵
- What are you doing? - I'm going for help.
宝贝 你会冻死的
Baby, you'll freeze to death.
我是最强壮的滑雪者 我准备好了
I'm the strongest skier. I've got the gear.
我会滑下山 然后找警察
I'll make it down the mountain, and I'll call the police.
- 宝贝 我真的觉得你不该这样行动 - 我走了
- Baby, I really don't think you should go. - I'm going.
要是没人可以做到 就让劳伦去做
If anybody can make it, it's Lauren.
我会回来找你的 好吗？我保证
I'll come back for you. Okay? I promise.
小心点
Be careful.
那我们该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
我很快会看见你的
I'll see you soon.
那现在呢？
And now what?
拜托 莎拉 拜托！我们不能返回去
Please, Sara, please! We can't go back in there.
- 我们必须回去 - 不
- We have to. - No.
这间医生的办公室…有坚固的门并且还有一把锁
The doctor's office…It has a sturdy door and a lock on it.
好吧 进来是对的
All right, it's right near the entrance.
- 我不能那样做 - 我们可以冻死 或者互相打死
- I can't do that. - We either freeze to death or we fight.
那是个计划
That's the plan.
好的
Okay.
- 我们要找到些武器 - 我找到了
- We have to get weapons. - I've got mine.
他们也需要这些武器
The rest of us need them too.
这太疯狂了 我们要离开这该死的地方！
This is crazy. We need to get the hell out of here!
风暴间歇期间 我们有事情要做
As soon as the storm breaks, that's what we're gonna do.
几位？过来 看看这个
Guys? Guys, look at this.
就是这个在阳台上攻击克莱尔的家伙
This is the guy that attacked Claire on the balcony.
他们极端暴力 无论是心理上 身体上都非常的畸形
It says they were violent, mentally, physically deformed…
向我们展示了同类相食的种种可怕的场景
and showed signs of cannibalism.
- 他们是怎么幸存在这个世界上的？ - 他们是猎犬
- How did they survive out here? - They're hunters.
现在他们开始猎食我们了 他们会吃掉任何的东西
And now they're hunting us. They'll eat anything.
该死！他们大概现在已经吃到波特的排骨了
Fuck! They probably turned Porter into porterhouse by now.
你闭嘴吧！
Just shut up!
地下室
The basement.
- 笼子里有东西 - 什么？
- That cage thing. - What?
是的 是的
Yes. Yes.
那个笼子下面有很多的小刀和锯子
That cage downstairs with all the knives and saws in it.
- 我们应该待在一起 - 不 我不这么认为
- We should all go together. - No, I don't think so.
让我们待在这里直到有人来帮我们
Let's just stay here until help comes.
看 你的妞待在这怎么样 丹尼尔和我要走了
Look, how about you girls stay here. Daniel and I will go.
- 你锁好门待在我们后面 - 哇！
- You lock the door behind us. - Whoa!
- 谢谢你愿意陪着我 - 我们需要这么做
- Thanks for volunteering me. - We need to do this.
我…我只是觉得我们应该待在一起 多给他们点信心
I-I just think we should all go together. Strength in numbers.
你不会是想临阵退缩吧？
You seriously gonna chicken out on me?
很好
Fine.
- 很好 我去吧 - 好的
- Fine. I'll go. - Good.
- 我和你一起走 - 不 不要
- I'll go with you. - No. Don't.
我没事的 你和肯尼娅待在一起吧
I'll be fine. You stay here with Kenia.
莎拉 请别走
Sara, please. Don't.
你知道之前我马上就回来
I'll be right back before you know it.
好吗？
Okay?
准备好了吗 各位？
Ready, guys?
我已经准备好了
Ready as I'll ever be.
锁好门
Lock the door.
这里不是非常的远 从左面还是可以上来的
It's not much further. It's just up here to the left.
那里怎么了？
What the fuck was that?
跑！
Run!
- 我们打死他 - 他手里拿着一把斧头！
- Let's just fight him! - He's got a fucking ax!
跑啊！
Just run!
在那里！
Over here.
- 他来了 我们杀了他 - 杀死那些畜生
- He's coming. Let's kill him. - Kill the lights.
凯尔？是你么？
Kyle? Is that you?
莎拉？丹尼尔？是你吗？
Sara? Daniel? Is that you?
救救我！
Help me!
他不会让你走的！
He won't let go!
救救我！
Help me!
快走开 你这个不要脸的家伙！
Go away, you motherfucker!
他走开了
He's going away.
- 别打开门 - 我们去找其他人
- Don't open the door. - We gotta get back to the others.
真他们的该死
Fuck him.
要是他敢回来 我们就会杀死他
If he comes back, we'll kill him.
来吧 来吧！
Come on. Come on!
嘘！
Shh!
没有危险 我们走
It's clear. Let's go.
甜心
Sweet.
让我走 你这个该死的怪胎！
Let me go, you fucking freaks!
肯尼娅？是我们 你没事吧？
Kenia? It's us. Are you okay?
- 该死的 发生什么事了？ - 快点！
- What the fuck happened? - Hurry!
开门！开门！
Open up! Open up!
太好了
Yeah.
丹尼尔哪去了？
Where's Daniel?
他在我后边
He was right behind me.
- 我们一定要回去找他 - 不 不 不！
- We have to go back for him. - No, no, no!
去外边太危险了 他们应该找到他了
It's dangerous out there. They could have got him.
开门 如果他在后边的话 我们会看见的
Open the door. We'll just see if he fell behind.
丹尼尔？丹尼尔？
Daniel? Daniel?
我没看见他
I don't see him.
好的 我们必须想出该怎么做
Okay, we gotta figure out what to do.
不！不！不！哦！
No! No! No! Oh!
哦 我的上帝！天 快来人救救我！
Oh, God! God, somebody help me!
快来人救救我！
Somebody help me!
我刺伤了他的手臂 然后离开了
I stabbed him in the arm, and he left.
嘘！你听到了吗？
Shh! Did you hear that?
是丹尼尔 我们必须帮帮他 我们还等什么呢？
It's Daniel. We've gotta help him. What are we waiting for?
听！
Listen!
去你的！
Fuck you!
救…
Help…
他大概已经死了
He's probably dead already.
如果他没有死 我可不想离开他自己走掉
I'm not gonna leave him out there if he isn't.
听！我们必须有一个计划
Listen! We have to have a plan…
如果我们能够活着离开这儿 那么我有一个计划
if we're gonna get out of here alive, and I have one.
包括离开丹尼尔让他死掉的计划？
Does it include leaving Daniel to die?
如果他们已经抓到了丹尼尔 布丽姬特也许是对的
If they have Daniel already, Bridget's probably right.
但是如果他藏起来了的话 我们需要计划一下
But if he's hiding, we need to be organized…
- 我们计划俘虏这些怪胎 - 怎么做？
- and have a plan to capture these freaks. - How?
啊！哦！哦！不 不！
Aaah! Oh! Oh! No, no!
你他妈的在做什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
- 就是他 我们走 - 不！那可能是个圈套
- That's him. Let's go. - No! It could be a trap.
- 什么？ - 那可能是个圈套
- What? - It could be a trap.
快来人救救我！
Somebody help me!
他们抓到了他 然后把他当做一个诱饵来把我们一个一个都抓起来
They have him, and he's the bait to get to the rest of us.
她说的对 为什么他们会让他活着？
She is right. Why else would they keep him alive?
我不关心她是不是说得对 我同意凯尔个莎拉的意见 你觉得呢？
I don't care if she's right. I agree with Kyle and Sara, okay?
- 我们让他自生自灭 - 一分钟前 你可不是这样说的
- We can't leave him to die. - Just a minute ago, you said not to go.
是啊 那时候我在想他可能已经死了 现在我知道他还活着
Yeah, that's when I thought he was dead. Now I know he's alive.
好吧 那我们投票
Fine. I say we vote.
什么？
What?
想留在这里的 举手
Those who want to stay, raise your hand.
想去救克莱尔的
Those who want to go.
好吧 我们走
Fine. Let's go.
- 你到了吗？ - 这里
- What do you got? - Here.
- 来吧 - 来吧 你准备好了吗？
- Come on. - Come on. You ready?
来吧
Come on.
他在地下室
He's in the basement.
他们到底在对他做什么？
What the hell are they doing to him?
天！天啊 让我…让我去死吧
God! God, let me… Let me die.
天 让我去死吧
God, let me die!
等等！等等！看看我们到什么地方来了
Wait! Wait! Think what's down there.
- 啊 这是C区域？ - 厨具和房间都是C区域
- Uh, the cell ward "C"? - The kitchen and cell ward "C".
- 我去看看 - 尽快回到我们这里
- I'll go check it out. - You come back to us.
完成
Done.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
天啊 让我…
God, let me…
抱歉 天啊 快让我去死吧！
I'm sorry. God, let me die!
天啊 请…
God, please…
他在哪？
Where is he?
他在那该死的厨房
He's in the fucking kitchen.
他们把他绑在桌子上 真让人害怕
They strapped him to a table. It was fucking horrible.
什么？
What?
他们割掉丹尼尔身上的衣服 把他身上的肉切成薄片
They're stripping pieces of flesh off of Daniel.
把薄片烫熟 然后一点点的吃掉
They're boiling it in oil, and they're eating him.
他们活吃着他 还加上奶酪火锅大杂烩
They're eating him alive like some fucked-up fondue.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
那里有多少人？
How many are in there?
三个人 有一个大家伙 还有两个臭小子
There's three. There's one big guy and two small guys.
詹娜 你先去 你先去走廊C区域的拐角处躲着
Jenna, you take that. You go down the hall to the juncture with Ward "C."
我们让他们从厨房的后门出去
We'll force them out the back door of the kitchen.
当他们向你走过来的时候 你就向他们扔油灯 好吧？
When they come to you, you throw the lamp. Okay?
- 他们没得选择只能下到房间区域里来 - 好的
- They're gonna have no choice but to go down to the cell ward. - Okay.
- 你准备好了吗？ - 让我们快走吧！
- Are you ready? - Let's fucking go.
准备好了吗？ 走！
Ready? Let's go!
快点！
Come on!
让我们杀了他们
Let's kill them.
- 好吧 开始动手吧 - 等等 我们不能就这么杀了他们
- Yes. Let's do it. - Wait. We can't just kill them.
什么？为什么不行？
What? Why the fuck not?
他们杀了我们的朋友 他们又想杀掉我们 还有吃掉我们
They killed our friends, and they were gonna kill us and fuckin' eat us.
是啊 我们不是他们
Yeah, we're not them.
别这样！嘿 你 看看我
Fuck that! Hey, you. Look at me.
看看我
Look at me.
去你的 去你妈的混蛋！
Fuck you, you motherfuckers!
我想砍断你的头！你理解吗？
I'm gonna cut your fucking hearts out! You understand that?
去拿别的煤油灯
Go get the other kerosene lantern.
我们想要烧烤这些活着的怪胎
We're gonna roast these fuckers alive.
烤肉时间 怪胎们
Time for a barbecue, fuckers.
凯尔 别这样做
Kyle, don't do this.
- 他们应得的报应 - 是的 他们应得…
- They deserve it. - Yeah, they do…
但是你不应该这样做
but you don't.
你别对自己这样做
Don't do this to yourself.
把那个打火机给我
Give me that lighter.
把打火机给我
Give me the lighter.
好的 我们要怎么办？
Okay. What the hell are we gonna do now?
我们要找电源线 然后早上离开这里
We find the spark plug wires, and we leave in the morning…
风暴 也许没有风暴
storm or no storm.
哪里有电源线？
Where are the spark plug wires?
这些私生子不会说话
The bastards can't even talk.
好吧 那就去找 一个房间一个房间去找
Fine. Then we search. Room by room.
好的 但是有人必须监视他们
Okay. But somebody has to watch them.
我来
I will.
我不想碰他们头上的头发 好吗？
I won't touch a fucking hair on their head. Okay?
好的
Okay.
去找电线
Go look for the wires.
我监视几个小时 然后再依次监视
Send someone back in a couple hours to relieve me.
我们今晚轮班监视
We'll take shifts throughout the night.
嘿 你
Hey, you.
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
过来 带点吃的
Come on, take it.
去你的 你他妈的混蛋！
Fuck you, motherfucker!
你以为我竟然会饲养你？
You thought I was actually gonna feed you?
我真想杀了你们三个 知道吗？
You know I'm actually gonna kill all three of you, don't you?
我会的
I will.
我想说 我想忘了这些事情
I'm gonna say I forgot something…
我想回去
and then I'm gonna come back…
我想杀了你们每一个怪胎
and I'm gonna kill each and every one of you freaks.
只是快点睡觉吧
Just sleep tight.
这里什么东西都没有
There's nothing here.
各位 这个地方太大了
Guys, this place is so big…
我们肯定找不到\r
we're never gonna find them.
我想说我们找另一个房间 继续看着
I say we pick another room and keep looking.
不 我们需要保持精力
No. We need our strength.
要是我们不能整晚监视的话 我们明天就会很糟
If we look all night, we're gonna be no good for tomorrow.
是的 但是要是我们不能找到电源线 我们就没办法离开
Yeah, but if we can't find the spark plug wires we can't leave.
我们在黎明之前要出去
I'm walking out of here at dawn.
让我们看看医生办公室 再到那去睡吧
Let's head up to the doctor's office and bed down for the night.
半夜换我来监视
I'll take the next watch.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
该换凯尔睡一下了
I'm gonna relieve Kyle of his shift.
小心
Be careful.
我会的 你也是
I will. You too.
我走后你要锁好门 知道吗？
You want to lock it after me?
我会的
I got it.
好的
Okay.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
哦 该死
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
只有这一个发电机 只有这一个发电机
It's only the generator. It's only the generator.
哦 天！
Oh, God!
凯尔？
Kyle?
妈的
Fuck.
凯尔？
Kyle?
哦 该死！该死的
Oh, shit! Shit.
是肯尼娅！快来！让我进去！
It's Kenia! Hurry! Let me in!
来吧 快来！
Come on, hurry!
- 来吧 来吧 - 发生什么事了？
- Come on. Come on. - What happened?
- 不见了 - 不见了？
- Gone. - Gone?
那三个怪胎 他们不见了
The three freaks, they're gone.
- 凯尔呢？ - 他也不见了 一点声音都没有
- And Kyle? - He's gone too. There's no sign of him.
- 什么？ - 你觉得凯尔把他们都杀了？
- What? - Do you think Kyle killed them?
不觉得 要是他杀了那些家伙的话 他就会在这里了不是么？
No. Wouldn't he be here right now if he did?
好的 我们必须从这里出去
Okay, we have to get out of here now.
我们用障碍物把这里堵起来到早上 然后我们就快点跑出去
We stay barricaded in until morning, and then we make a run for it.
都同意吧？
Everyone agree?
好的 如果我们到时候都搞定了的话
Okay, if we make it till then.
- 你听到没？ - 听到了
- Did you hear that? - Yes.
我想出去检查一下
I'm gonna go check it out.
别太接近了
Don't get too close.
- 那是谁？ - 是其中一个小个子的
- Who is it? - It's the small one.
他没有武器 我们杀了他吧
He's unarmed. Let's fucking kill him.
这很奇怪 这可能是一个圈套
This is strange. This could be a trap.
- 其他两个可能在角落里 - 但如果他们不在呢？
- The other two could be around the corner. - But what if they're not?
我们可以杀了一个增加我们逃出去的可能
We can kill one right now and improve our odds.
我们杀了那个怪物！
Let's fucking kill him!
我们这里有四个人 他们那里却只有一个人 我们快动手
There are four of us, and there's one of him. Let's fucking do it.
好的
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
好的 但是我们要一起行动 然后再回来
Okay, but we go as a group, and we come right back here.
- 你准备好了吗？ - 准备好了
- You ready? - Yes.
开始吧
Let's go.
你这个变态去死吧！
You fuckin' pervert, die!
去死！去死 你这个混蛋！
Die! Die, motherfucker!
哦 不！不 求求你 不要！不 不 不！
Oh, no! No, please, no! No, no, no!
为什么他什么话都不说？
Why didn't he say anything?
因为那些私生子砍掉了他的舌头
Because the bastards cut his tongue out.
我们得回去！
We gotta get back!
我们中了圈套
We're trapped in here.
他们来了！快上楼！
They're coming! Upstairs, quick!
去 我们要藏进阁楼里去 走！
Go. We'll hide in the attic. Go!
这是他们居住的地方
This is where they live.
他们快回来了 我们快离开这里
And where they'll come back to. Let's get out of here.
是的 现在就离开
Yeah, now.
看 外套 拿些工具
Look, coats. Grab some gear.
- 不 我不要披着这些脏衣服 - 哦 是的 当然
- No, I'm not putting those clothes on. - Oh, yes, you are.
- 我们能够在这里幸存下来 - 带上这个
- We can survive in these. - Take this.
- 快点 - 我们走吧
- Hurry! - Let's go.
走下主楼 看看我们能不能找到一条出去的路
Head down to the main floor. See if we can find a way out.
我们找到一个开着的门
We've got to find a way to lock ourselves in.
快躲起来
Here. Here. Go.
那里 那应该等他们在外面的时候
There. That should keep them out for a while.
我们需要找到从这里离开的路
We need to find a way to get out of here.
我们必须从窗户上爬出去
We have to climb out a window.
- 好的 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
铁栅栏 我们被干了
Grates. We're fucked.
他们不会待在铁栅栏里
They can't all be grated.
让那些畸形者进来？你确信就是他们
To keep the freaks in? You bet they all are.
- 嘿 各位 过来 - 什么？
- Hey, everyone. Come here. - What?
栅栏已经生锈了 把手给我
The grate has rusted out. Give me a hand.
小心
Careful.
该死！
Shit!
这些混蛋在门那里！
The fuckers are at the door.
快点！
Hurry!
退后
Stand back.
我挖了一个洞 你们跟着来
I'll dig a hole. You guys follow.
快 快 快！
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
快点！
Hurry!
我出去了
I'm out.
- 你是下一个 走吧 - 好
- You're next. Get going. - Okay.
快点走吧 我们在后面见
Get going. I'll be right behind.
明白！
Clear!
快点 肯尼娅！快点！快！快！
Come on, Kenia! Come on! Hurry! Hurry!
我安全了！来吧 詹娜 快点！
I'm clear! Come on, Jenna. Hurry!
快！
Now!
詹娜 你能听得到吗？
Jenna, can you hear me?
抓住我的脚踝
Hold my ankles.
让我出去！
Get me out of here!
- 詹娜？詹娜？ - 不！
- Jenna? Jenna? - No.
快点！我们要走了！
Come on! We gotta get going!
快点！快点！起来！我们必须快点走！
Come on! Come on! Get up! We have to go!
来吧！我们得快点！
Come on! We've gotta keep going!
跟着我 跟紧我
Follow me. Stay close.
快点！
Come on!
我们必须快速行动！跑！
We've got to move quicker! Run!
- 他们拿了我们的雪地摩托 - 快！快！
- They got our snowmobiles. - Move! Move!
继续跑！
Keep going!
让我走！
Go away!
求求你！让我走！
Please! Go away!
不！
No!
他们去哪了？
Where are they going?
谁在乎？快点！
Who cares? Come on!
能停一下吗？
Can you stop?
我丢掉了铁栅栏旁的棍子 我要回去找到它
I dropped the fireplace poker.I gotta go back and find it.
- 我们已经没有时间那样做了 - 这是很好的武器 我们需要它
- We don't have time for that.- It's a good weapon. We need it.
- 和布丽姬特待在一起 - 好吗？我去去就回
- Stay with Bridget, okay? - I've gotta go back.
来吧！来吧！
Come on! Come on!
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
- 他们都从两个方向来的 - 什么？
- They're coming in both directions. - What?
- 我没看见什么光线 - 他们把这些关掉了
- I don't see any lights. - They turned them off.
躺下 藏起来 躺下
Get down and hide. Get down.
- 我不能这么做 我不能这么做 - 躺下
- I can't do this. I can't do this. - Get down.
我做不到
I can't do it.
布丽姬特！
Bridget!
不！
No!
肯尼娅？有多糟？
Kenia? How bad is it?
我不知道 好像受伤了
I don't know. It fucking hurts.
- 快点 快点 - 他们找到布丽姬特了
- Come on. Come on. - They got Bridget.
好的 让我们去林木线那里
Okay, let's get you to the tree line.
那我回去找她 好吗？ 来吧
Then I'll go back for her, okay? Come on.
我们准备把你的外套脱下来
We've gotta get your jacket off.
妈的
Ow! Fuck.
- 就这样吧 - 准备好了吗？
- Just do it. - You ready?
好的 宝贝
Okay, baby.
血应该出的很慢
That should slow the bleeding.
去找她
Go find her.
你会一直都待着这儿的？
You'll be all right here?
- 我一直都在这里的 好么？ - 好的
- I'll be right here. Okay? - Okay.
布丽姬特！你在哪里？布丽姬特？
Bridget! Where are you, Bridget?
坚持一下！布丽姬特 我来了！
Hang on! Bridget, I'm coming!
莎拉？
Sara?
布丽姬特？
Bridget?
布丽姬特！
Bridget!
布丽姬特？莎拉？
Bridget? Sara?
莎拉 莎拉
Sara. Sara.
哦 我的天！
Oh, my God!
不！不！布丽姬特？
No! No! Bridget?
莎拉！你在哪？
Sara! Where are you?
莎拉！
Sara!
哦 我的天！
Oh, my God!
莎拉！
Sara!
请…救救我！
Please… Please help me!
随便谁
Anyone.
不 不！
No. No!
不！
No!
莎拉！
Sara!
太好了！它启动了
Yes! It worked.
做的不错
Good job.
让我们离开这个地狱吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
哦 不！
Oh, no!